Turkus, Burton B. Arbitration Files 5712
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Sealand Services, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  11/23/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - negligence and carelessness. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. All Offshore Contract Companies., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  6/9/81. Issue: Fringe benefits. Includes: Supporting documentation, correspondence.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Amerada Hess Corporation., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  2/11/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - incompetence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Hudson Waterways, Inc., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  9/17/80. Issue: Seniority. Includes: Correspondence, exhibits.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization vs. Sealand Services, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  3/2/81. Issue: Transfer - incompetence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots, International Organization. General File (Box 13, Folder 1-9)
  includes unidentifiable exhibits, certification of referendum, other documents, forms, correspondence regarding billing statements, miscellaneous items
- Maxwell Plum International vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  5/21/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Cancelled
- Menorah Home and Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  6/8/81. Issue: withdrawn.
- Methodist Hospital of Brooklyn vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  7/26/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination - threats. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Metropolitan Dade County Employers vs. AFSCME, Local 1363, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  6/3/76. Issue: Schedules of Work - workweek. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, briefs, correspondence, legal documents, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Metropolitan Jewish Geriatric Care Center vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  5/26/81. Issue: withdrawn.
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Agency vs. Insurance Workers International, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14a)
  10/11/68. Issue: Discharge - misconduct. Includes: Award only
- Metropolitan Transportation Authority vs. IBT, Local 808, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  4/30/79. Issue: Union security - agency shop. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, legal documents, exhibits.
- Meyers Parking System, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 272, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  10/5/77. Issue: Supervisors and foremen - inclusion in bargaining unit. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits.
- Midland-Ross Corporation vs. IAM, Lodge 329, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  4/27/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, briefs.
- Midway Aircraft Instrument Corporation vs. IAM, Lodge 142, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  7/22/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercations. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, legal documents
- Milano Food, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 6, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  8/13/82. Issue: withdrawn
- Millar Elevator Industries, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 3, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  11/17/76. Issue: Assignment of job - bargaining unit work. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- Mobil Oil Corporation vs. OCAW, Local 8-801, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  9/21/75. Issue: withdrawn.
- Mobil Oil Corporation vs. OCAW, Local 8-766, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  10/10/79. Issue: withdrawn.
- Mobil Oil Corporation vs. OCAW, Local 8-801, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  6/26/79. Issue: Employment - disability. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Mobil Oil Corporation vs. Petroleum Association of Labor, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 23a)
  10/14/68. Issue: Safety - plant rules. Includes: Award only.
- Montrex Corporation vs. International Jewelry Workers Union, Local 1, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  3/11/77. Issue: Subcontracting. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  11/6/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - misconduct - timeliness of grievance. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, transcripts, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  9/8/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - unauthorized absences. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits, legal documents.
- Morrisania Affiliation vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  3/28/77. Issue: Discipline - suspension - illegal possession of drugs - police record - back pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Motion Picture Laboratory Technicians vs. IATSE, Local 702, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  11/11/76. Issue: Discipline - suspension - negligence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, briefs.
- Mount Sinai Hospital vs. NYSNA, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  6/3/77. Issue: withdrawn
- Mount Sinai Hospital vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  10/13/76. Issue: withdrawn.
- Mount Sinai Hospital vs. NYSNA, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  5/5/81. Issue: withdrawn
- Nabisco, Inc. vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 719, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  5/14/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - work stoppage. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation, legal documents.
- Nabisco, Inc. vs. BCWIU, Local 719, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  8/14/78. Issue: Fights and altercations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Nabisco, Inc. vs. BCWIU, Local 719, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  8/22/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Award only.
- National Airlines, Inc. vs. Transport Workers, Local 555, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  11/27/78. Issue: Contract interpretation - representation. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- National Airlines, Inc. vs. Transport Workers, Local 555, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  2/25/80. Issue: Contract interpretation - schedules of work. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- National Airlines, Inc. vs. Transport Workers, Local 555, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  3/10/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- National Airlines, Inc. vs. Transport Workers, Local 555 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Not dated. Includes: Correspondence regarding System Board of Adjustment for National Airlines.
- National Airlines, Inc. vs. Transport Workers, Local 555, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  2/14/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits.
- National Airlines, Inc. vs. Transport Workers, Local 555, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  11/27/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules. Includes: Exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- National Broadcasting Company vs. NABET, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  1/22/76. Issue: withdrawn
- National Can Company vs. IBT, Local 202, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  1/13/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - assignment of job - physical qualifications - insubordination. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- National Cash Register Corporation vs. Allied Service Division, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  6/20/77. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- National Elevator Industry, Inc. vs. International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  1/12/76. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- National Heat and Power Corporation vs. IBT, Local 553, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13a)
  7/9/73. Issue: Vacation pay. Includes: Award only.
- National Maritime Union vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  5/3/77. Issue: withdrawn.
- Nazareth Regional High School vs. AFT, Local 1261, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  4/6/81. Issue: Evaluation of job factors - change in operations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, legal documents, exhibits.
- New England Telephone Company vs. CWA, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  3/28/80. Issue: withdrawn
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  6/17/82. Issue: Absence - insubordination. Includes: Correspondence, exhibits.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  8/17/79. Issue: withdrawn.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  5/4/81. Issue: Absences - disability - termination. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, transcripts, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  5/16/82. Issue: withdrawn.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2321, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  6/30/81. Issue: Demotion - health and disability. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, transcripts, supporting documentation, exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- New England Telephone Company vs. CWA, Local 1303, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  1/7/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - drugs, sale and use. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  10/15/79. Issue: cancelled.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, System Council T-6, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  3/18/81. Issue: Settled during hearing
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  8/23/78. Issue: settled
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  8/30/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - negligence and carelessness. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  7/22/82. Issue: Discharge - suspension - unsatisfactory work. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, transcripts, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  7/27/82. Issue: settled.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  8/4/82. Issue: Suspension - leaving work area without permission - insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, transcripts, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  1/28/80. Issue: Discipline - termination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  12/15/75. Issue: Discipline - termination - improper job attitude - fights and altercation. Includes: Award only.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  6/16/82. Issue: Discipline - termination - plant rules - leaving work area without permission - theft. Includes: Exhibits, legal documents, supporting documentation.
- New England Telephone Company vs. IBEW, Local 2222 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Includes: Miscellaneous documents regarding various cases
- New Jersey Telephone Company vs. CWA, Local 1075, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  12/30/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - rates of pay - holidays - falsification of records. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, supporting documentation.
- New School for Social Research vs. IBT, Local 1518, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  12/12/78. Issue: Rates of pay - classification of job - temporary employee. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- New York, City of vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  8/3/81. Issue: Working conditions - accident - pension plan - shift differential. Includes: Transcripts, exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- New York Gaslight Club, Inc. vs. Dining Room Employees, Local 1, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  8/14/75. Includes: No Award.
- New York Gaslight Club, Inc. vs. Dining Room Employees, Local 1, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  8/13/73. Issue: Improper personal conduct - fights and altercations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- New York Institute of Technology vs. IBT, Local 80, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  5/13/77. Issue: Call-in - error - management rights. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- New York Public Library vs. AFSCME, District Council 37, Local 1930, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  8/3/77. Issue: Mental Illness - detrimental conduct - profanity. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- New York Public Library vs. AFSCME, District Council 37, Local 1930, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  4/9/79. Issue: Discipline - suspension - improper job attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits
- New York Public Library vs. AFSCME, District Council 37, Local 1930, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  12/17/79. Issue: withdrawn.
- New York Racing Association vs. Independent Association of Mutual Employees of New York State, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 15a)
  3/31/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Improper personal conduct - theft. Includes: Award only.
- New York Racing Association vs. IBEW, Local 3, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  2/15/79. Issue: Strike, slowdown, work stoppage. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- New York Shipping Association (John C. Mandel Security Bureau, Inc.) vs. ILWA, Port Watchmen's Union, Local 1456, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  6/29/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - sleeping on job. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- New York Shipping Association vs. ILA, Local 1, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  7/26/82. Includes: No Award.
- New York Shipping Association vs. ILA, Local 791, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  11/8/76. Issue: Vacations - eligibility - scheduling. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation, legal documents.
- New York Shipping Association vs. ILA, Local 1, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  7/15/76. Issue: Elimination of job - management rights. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, legal documents, supporting documentation.
- New York Subways Advertising Company, Inc. vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  5/23/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- New York Telephone Company vs. Telephone Traffic Union, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  8/4/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - unsatisfactory work. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits.
- New York University Medical Center vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  5/27/76. Issue: Rates of pay - rate revision. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Third Garage Company vs. IBT, Local 2, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  8/24/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination - fights and altercations - disloyalty. Issue: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 143, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  10/6/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - drinking on job. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 143, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  9/22/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job conduct - falsification of records. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 143, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  4/15/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Unauthorized absences. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  5/20/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules - alcoholism, drinking prior to reporting. Includes: Award only.
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 143, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  4/18/80. Issue: Posting - vacancies. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 143, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  3/5/80. Issue: Discharge - insubordination - theft - absences -falsification of records. Settled. Includes: Settlement Agreement, exhibits, correspondence, briefs.
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. BRAC, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  4/7/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Improper personal conduct - dishonesty - fraud. Includes: Award only.
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 143, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  1/17/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Improper job conduct. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- North Shore Nursing Home vs. Nursing Home and Hospital Employees, Local 1115, Joint Board, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  5/24/79. Issue: Discipline - Suspension - pending court action. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- North Shore Nursing Home vs. Nursing Home and Hospital Employees, Local 1115, Joint Board, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  3/8/76. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation. No Award.
- Oak Beverages, Inc. vs. IBT, Soft Drink Workers Union, Local 812, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  7/20/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - misconduct. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Oak Beverages, Inc. vs. IBT, Soft Drink Workers Union, Local 812, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  3/23/81. Issue: Rate of pay - contract interpretation. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Ogden Food Service Corporation vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  9/15/82. Issue: settled
- Ogden Food Service Corporation vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  4/13/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude -general attitude.
- Ogden Food Service Corporation vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 69, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  9/28/78. Issue: settled
- Ogden Food Service Corporation vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 178, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  9/5/73. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty - plant rules. Includes: Award only.
- Old London Foods vs. IBT, Local 138, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  2/26/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge - safety - accident. Includes: Award only.
- Overseas National Airways, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 295, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  1/19/76. Issue: Rate of pay - schedules of work - overtime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Owens-Illinois, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 15, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  3/7/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Absences. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Owners Maintenance Corporation vs. SEIU, Local 32J, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
  9/1/78. Issue: Absences - contract interpretation. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits. No Award.
- Pakistan International Airlines Corporation vs. IBT, Local 851, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  1/8/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - negligence - misconduct. Issue: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Pan American World Airways vs. Labor Protective Provisions Claim, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  11/19/82. Includes: No Award.
- Pan American World Airways vs. Transport Workers, Local 504, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  10/21/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, legal documents, supporting documentation.
- Pan American World Airways vs. Transport Workers of America, Local 504, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  8/31/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, City of New York, New York (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Not dated. Issue: Certification election. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Penn Dixie Cement Company vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers, Local 65 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  Not dated. Issue: Plant shutdown - contracting-out. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Penn Industries, Inc. vs. ILA, Local 976, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  4/3/81. Issue: Seniority. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits.
- Pepsi-Cola Company vs. ILA, Local 1476, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18a)
  2/11/74. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Absences. Includes: Award only.
- Pepsi-Cola Metropolitan Bottling Company vs. IBT, Local 812, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 18b)
  8/5/70. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Absences - reporting. Includes: Award only.
- Perma Line Corporation of America vs. International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Local 230, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  3/16/81. Issue: Rates of Pay - overtime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Petroleum Association of Labor vs. Mobil Oil Corporation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 19a)
  10/14/68. Issue: Absences. Includes: Award only.
- Petroleum Heat and Power Company vs. Petroleum Workers Association, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  4/21/76. Issue: Promotion - seniority. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Phelps Dodge vs. USA, Local 4355, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  11/4/82. Includes: No Award
- Playboy Club of New York vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 6, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  8/26/82. Issue: settled.
- Playboy Club of New York vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 6, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  12/14/79. Issue: Discharge - absences. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Playboy Club of New York vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 1, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  7/20/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - misconduct - improper job attitude - negligence. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Playboy Clubs International vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 69, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  12/20/76. Issue: Certification election. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Playboy of Sussex, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 69, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Playboy Club of New York vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 6, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  1/26/82. Issue: Schedules of work. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, legal documents, exhibits.
- Playboy of Sussex, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union, Local 69, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  2/21/78. Issue: Certification election.
- Port Authority of New York and New Jersey vs. Port Authority Police Benevolent Association, Inc., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)